<matchmbm timestamp="2010-06-15T15:46:10.9769911+01:00" mbmValid="1"><allevents><e id="29150100" code="14" ph="1" min="999998" sec="0" phmin="45" tag="mbm_endfirsthalf" /><e id="29149770" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="45" sec="0" phmin="45" timedisplay="45' "><descr>Another disappointing corner from Côte d'Ivoire - how many of those have we seen so far today and at the tournament in general? The headed goals in today's earlier match came from excellent crosses, but both were from open play. Time for the set piece specialists to step up.</descr></e><e id="29149410" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="42" sec="0" phmin="42" timedisplay="42' "><descr>It's all become a bit scrappy at the moment. Is fear of defeat greater than desire for victory at this stage of the competition? Both sides here certainly seem to be affording the other a great deal of respect.</descr></e><e id="29149450" code="10" t_id="43854" pl_id="3355" pl_idTo="3355" t_idTo="43854" x="1000" y="999" fz="ORA" ph="1" min="41" sec="56" phmin="42" timedisplay="42' " tag="mbm_corner1" /><e id="29149220" code="11" t_id="43963" pl_id="210229" pl_idTo="198051" t_idTo="43854" x="437" y="874" fz="MD" ph="1" min="40" sec="40" phmin="41" timedisplay="41' " tag="mbm_foul2" /><e id="29149040" code="11" t_id="43963" pl_id="210214" pl_idTo="213910" t_idTo="43854" x="512" y="102" fz="MA" ph="1" min="39" sec="54" phmin="40" timedisplay="40' " tag="mbm_foul1" /><e id="29148910" code="55" st="G" t_id="43854" pl_id="213910" pl_idTo="210229" t_idTo="43963" x="474" y="812" fz="MD" ph="1" min="38" sec="5" phmin="39" timedisplay="39' " /><e id="29148440" code="11" t_id="43963" pl_id="269784" pl_idTo="176984" t_idTo="43854" x="637" y="51" fz="MA" ph="1" min="36" sec="25" phmin="37" timedisplay="37' " tag="mbm_foul3" /><e id="29148020" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="35" sec="0" phmin="35" timedisplay="35' "><descr>Chances are few and far between, but there is no shortage of quality out there. This looks to be one of the most evenly-matched games we have seen so far, although Ronaldo looks the most likely player to make something happen.</descr></e><e id="29147750" code="11" t_id="43854" pl_id="3355" pl_idTo="201200" t_idTo="43963" x="460" y="205" fz="MD" ph="1" min="32" sec="57" phmin="33" timedisplay="33' " tag="mbm_foul2" /><e id="29147460" code="11" t_id="43854" pl_id="291329" pl_idTo="199026" t_idTo="43963" x="654" y="287" fz="MA" ph="1" min="31" sec="59" phmin="32" timedisplay="32' " tag="mbm_foul1" /><e id="29147290" code="55" st="G" t_id="43854" pl_id="291329" pl_idTo="201200" t_idTo="43963" x="470" y="289" fz="MD" ph="1" min="30" sec="20" phmin="31" timedisplay="31' " /><e id="29146950" code="55" st="G" t_id="43854" pl_id="213910" pl_idTo="210229" t_idTo="43963" x="559" y="629" fz="MA" ph="1" min="27" sec="47" phmin="28" timedisplay="28' " /><e id="29146660" code="10" t_id="43854" pl_id="198051" pl_idTo="198051" t_idTo="43854" x="991" y="17" fz="OLA" ph="1" min="26" sec="38" phmin="27" timedisplay="27' " tag="mbm_corner2" /><e id="29146770" code="55" st="N" t_id="43963" pl_id="214957" pl_idTo="290186" t_idTo="43854" x="62" y="806" fz="ORD" ph="1" min="26" sec="34" phmin="27" timedisplay="27' " /><e id="29146190" code="11" t_id="43963" pl_id="210214" pl_idTo="176984" t_idTo="43854" x="346" y="344" fz="MD" ph="1" min="24" sec="9" phmin="25" timedisplay="25' " tag="mbm_foul3" /><e id="29146420" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="24" sec="0" phmin="24" timedisplay="24' "><descr>P. FERREIRA (POR) slides in to make a terrific saving tackle, denying GERVINHO (CIV) a shot on goal after the Côte d'Ivoire forward had wriggled through a couple of Portuguese challenges.</descr></e><e id="29145890" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="23" sec="0" phmin="23" timedisplay="23' "><descr>There's a booking apiece for DEMEL (CIV) and RONALDO (POR) following a set-to on the edge of the Ivorian penalty area. Let's hope we see all 22 players stay on the field.</descr></e><e id="29146180" code="55" st="N" t_id="43963" pl_id="187197" pl_idTo="290186" t_idTo="43854" x="100" y="671" fz="ARD" ph="1" min="22" sec="52" phmin="23" timedisplay="23' " /><e id="29145930" code="11" t_id="43854" pl_id="198106" pl_idTo="199026" t_idTo="43963" x="516" y="296" fz="MA" ph="1" min="22" sec="17" phmin="23" timedisplay="23' " tag="mbm_foul2" /><e id="29145900" code="11" t_id="43854" pl_id="3355" pl_idTo="210229" t_idTo="43963" x="515" y="188" fz="MA" ph="1" min="22" sec="8" phmin="23" timedisplay="23' " tag="mbm_foul1" /><e id="29145880" code="11" st="H" t_id="43963" pl_id="210229" x="770" y="807" fz="ORA" ph="1" min="21" sec="37" phmin="22" timedisplay="22' " tag="mbm_foul_h" /><e id="29145770" code="11" t_id="43854" pl_id="216970" pl_idTo="199026" t_idTo="43963" x="619" y="313" fz="MA" ph="1" min="21" sec="18" phmin="22" timedisplay="22' " tag="mbm_foul3" /><e id="29145410" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="21" sec="0" phmin="21" timedisplay="21' "><descr>The Ivorian line-up does, of course, include two brothers: Kolo and Yaya Toure. They have become the fourth pair of siblings to feature in successive FIFA World Cups together, following England’s Bobby and Jackie Charlton (1966-1970), Netherlands' Willy and Rene van de Kerkhof (1974-1978) and another Dutch pair: Frank and Ronald de Boer (1994-1998).</descr></e><e id="29145460" code="1" t_id="43854" pl_id="213910" pl_idTo="213910" t_idTo="43854" ph="1" min="20" sec="17" phmin="21" timedisplay="21' " tag="mbm_yellowcard3" /><e id="29145420" code="1" t_id="43963" pl_id="201200" pl_idTo="201200" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="20" sec="14" phmin="21" timedisplay="21' " tag="mbm_yellowcard2" /><e id="29144880" code="11" t_id="43854" pl_id="291329" pl_idTo="199026" t_idTo="43963" x="632" y="12" fz="MA" ph="1" min="17" sec="7" phmin="18" timedisplay="18' " tag="mbm_foul2" /><e id="29144620" code="7" t_id="43854" pl_id="291329" pl_idTo="291329" t_idTo="43854" x="815" y="201" fz="OLA" ph="1" min="16" sec="8" phmin="17" timedisplay="17' " tag="mbm_shotwide1" /><e id="29144380" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="16" sec="0" phmin="16" timedisplay="16' "><descr>We're still waiting on the first free-kick goal of this FIFA World Cup but TIENE (CIV) comes close to providing one with a curling left-foot shot that flashes wide of the right-hand post.</descr></e><e id="29143940" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="14" sec="0" phmin="14" timedisplay="14' "><descr>That's an early warning for Côte d'Ivoire, as if they needed one, of Ronaldo's capabilities. The Portugal No7 really looks to be in the mood.</descr></e><e id="29144180" code="7" st="1" t_id="43854" pl_id="3355" pl_idTo="3355" t_idTo="43854" x="739" y="721" fz="ORA" ph="1" min="13" sec="57" phmin="14" timedisplay="14' " tag="mbm_freekick_wide" /><e id="29143970" code="11" t_id="43963" pl_id="210213" pl_idTo="290186" t_idTo="43854" x="296" y="276" fz="MD" ph="1" min="13" sec="14" phmin="14" timedisplay="14' " tag="mbm_foul1" /><e id="29143730" code="9" t_id="43963" pl_id="313541" pl_idTo="313541" t_idTo="43963" x="848" y="84" fz="OLA" ph="1" min="11" sec="23" phmin="12" timedisplay="12' " tag="mbm_offside1" /><e id="29143770" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="11" sec="0" phmin="11" timedisplay="11' "><descr>What an effort from RONALDO (POR)! The world's most expensive player bursts into space 25 yards from goal and unleashes a superb right-foot shot that smacks off the outside of the post with BARRY (CIV) beaten.</descr></e><e id="29143670" code="8" st="T" t_id="43963" pl_id="201200" pl_idTo="201200" t_idTo="43963" x="703" y="495" fz="MA" ph="1" min="10" sec="29" phmin="11" timedisplay="11' " tag="mbm_shotgoal_t" /><e id="29143450" code="10" t_id="43963" pl_id="199026" pl_idTo="199026" t_idTo="43963" x="980" y="24" fz="OLA" ph="1" min="8" sec="5" phmin="9" timedisplay="9' " tag="mbm_corner1" /><e id="29143370" code="6" st="1" t_id="43963" pl_id="201200" pl_idTo="201200" t_idTo="43963" x="641" y="474" fz="MA" ph="1" min="7" sec="20" phmin="8" timedisplay="8' " tag="mbm_freekick_blocked" /><e id="29143140" code="1" t_id="43854" pl_id="176971" pl_idTo="176971" t_idTo="43854" ph="1" min="6" sec="33" phmin="7" timedisplay="7' " tag="mbm_yellowcard1" /><e id="29143090" code="11" t_id="43854" pl_id="176971" pl_idTo="201200" t_idTo="43963" x="359" y="545" fz="MD" ph="1" min="6" sec="25" phmin="7" timedisplay="7' " tag="mbm_foul3" /><e id="29142520" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="6" sec="0" phmin="6" timedisplay="6' "><descr>An early booking for ZOKORA (CIV), who dived in recklessly on  RONALDO (POR). The former Tottenham Hotspur midfielder has been picked in an unfamiliar central defensive role today.</descr></e><e id="29142900" code="11" t_id="43854" pl_id="216970" pl_idTo="201200" t_idTo="43963" x="564" y="0" fz="MA" ph="1" min="5" sec="10" phmin="6" timedisplay="6' " tag="mbm_foul2" /><e id="29142300" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="5" sec="0" phmin="5" timedisplay="5' "><descr>A tight opening few minutes, with a couple of crunching tackles already. Portugal, it's worth noting, have a fine record against African opposition; in fact, they are unbeatable in their last 12 encounters against African sides,a run that stretches back to 1986.</descr></e><e id="29142170" code="11" t_id="43963" pl_id="210214" pl_idTo="198051" t_idTo="43854" x="551" y="248" fz="MA" ph="1" min="1" sec="37" phmin="2" timedisplay="2' " tag="mbm_foul1" /><e id="29142120" code="13" ph="1" min="0" sec="0" phmin="1" tag="mbm_startfirsthalf" /><e id="29142090" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>The national anthems have been played and the captains have exchanged pennants. The action is now just seconds away. Let's hope this game lives up to expectations. If it does, we should be in for a cracker.</descr></e><e id="29141950" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>The teams are in the tunnel, side by side. Of the two, the Ivorians appear the more nervous, while Ronaldo is smiling and looking extremely relaxed.</descr></e><e id="29141910" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>The big kick-off is now less than 15 minutes away, so time to deliver your verdict: Côte d'Ivoire or Portugal? </descr></e><e id="29141890" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>Eriksson and Ronaldo are just two of the FIFA World Cup headliners we have spoke to in recent days. Check out our news and interviews section for words and wisdom from the likes of Cesc Fabregas, Landon Donovan and Andriy Arshavin.</descr></e><e id="29141840" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>Unlike Portugal, Côte d'Ivoire qualified for South Africa 2010 with some ease, and enter this tournament viewed by many as Africa's greatest hope. But what do you think? Which side from the Mother Continent is best equipped to challenge for the title at Africa's first-ever FIFA World Cup? Let us know on FanChat.</descr></e><e id="29141780" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>Portugal, of course, are coached by Carlos Queiroz, the man who led the nation's golden generation to glory at the FIFA U-20 World Cup. Replicating that feat at senior level is sure to prove difficult, but Queiroz - whose side so nearly missed out on these finals - believes his players are "determined to represent the best side in the world". </descr></e><e id="29141760" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>Eriksson has been in charge for just 74 days but, according to Kolo Toure, the Swede has already made a major impression. “Eriksson has put an added emphasis on playing as a team and not just as a collection of individuals," said the Manchester City centre-half. "He has managed to change the mindset of the squad and of each player. We’ve always had good players, but have never been able to properly work together as an effective unit, defending and attacking as one."</descr></e><e id="29141700" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>Ironically, Eriksson is making his FIFA World Cup comeback against the team responsible for eliminating his England side in 2006. Vengeance, however, is not on his mind. "Could this be revenge?" he said. "No I'm not thinking about that at all. Four years ago England were unlucky, we lost on penalties, but that's life."</descr></e><e id="29141560" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>There will also be considerable pressure on Sven-Goran Eriksson in this, his first competitive game in charge of Les Elephants. The former England coach was appointed in March and is returning to the tournament in which he led the Three Lions to the last eight in 2002 and 2006.</descr></e><e id="29140970" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>Ronaldo spoke to FIFA in the build-up to this match and suggested that Portugal should be seen as potential dark horses for the world title. "As I said before the finals, we’re not one of the favourites. But that doesn’t mean that a supposedly unfancied team can’t become world champions."</descr></e><e id="29140720" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>With Lionel Messi already having made an impressive debut at South Africa 2010, all eyes will be on Ronaldo to see if he can match his main rival for the title of world's greatest player. What's your view on that particular debate? Let us know on FanChat.</descr></e><e id="29139850" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>Portugal, meawhile, have left out Atletico Madrid winger Simao, and will ask the Brazil-born duo of Deco and Liedson to help shoulder the creative and goalscoring burden that rests on the team's captain and talisman, Cristiano Ronaldo.</descr></e><e id="29139660" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>In Drogba's absence, Sven-Goran Eriksson will look to Aruna Dindane and Gervinho to provide the Ivorian goal threat, while Yaya Toure is sure to be a key man in midfield.</descr></e><e id="29139290" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>The teams are in and, predictably, Didier Drogba finds himself at the centre of attention. The Chelsea striker has not recovered in time to take his place in the Elephants' starting line-up but he is among the substitutes and could well make his FIFA World Cup entrance here in Nelson Mandela Bay.</descr></e><e id="29138960" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>With group rivals Brazil considered by many to be tournament favourites, both of these of these sides have identified this match as absolutely vital to their chances of joining Dunga's side in the Round of 16.</descr></e><e id="29138640" code="21" t_id="43854" t_idTo="43963" ph="1" min="-1" sec="0" phmin="-1"><descr>Good afternoon and welcome to FIFA.com's EMIRATES MatchCast for Côte d'Ivoire's potentially thrilling encounter with Portugal. In Rustenburg, Slovakia look to be closing in on three points against New Zealand, but our focus will remain on what is arguably the game of the day. </descr></e></allevents></matchmbm>
